A Guide to the Minutes of the Advisory Board on Teacher Education and Licensure, 1998-2020
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Minutes of the Advisory Board on Teacher Education and Licensure, 1998-2020
The Library of Virginia
53733
.5 cu. ft. (2 boxes)
Advisory Board on Teacher Education and Licensure
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 53733 was transferred by the Virginia Dept. of Education, 30 Sept 2022.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Advisory Board on Teacher Education and Licensure advises the Board of Education and submits recommendations on policies applicable to the qualifications, examination, licensure, and regulation of school personnel including revocation, suspension, denial, cancellation, reinstatement, and renewals of licensure, fees for processing applications, standards for the approval of preparation programs, reciprocal approval of preparation programs, and other related matters as the Board of Education may request or the Advisory Board may deem necessary. The final authority for licensure of school personnel shall remain with the Board of Education.(Code of Virginia, 22.1-305.2)
Scope and Content
Minutes of the Virginia Advisory Board on Teacher Education and Licensure, 1998-2020, include draft and final minutes, agendas, and background information including correspondence and reports. Also includes operating procedures, 1998; and the Annual Report to the Board of Education, 2003.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in chronological order.
Contents List
- Minutes, 1998-2020.
  - Operating procedures, 1998. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agendas, 1998. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report to the Board of Education, 2003. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agendas, 2001. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 20. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2002. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2003. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2004. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2005. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2008. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2009. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2010. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2011. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2012. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2013. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2014. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2015. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2016. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2017. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2018. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2019. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2020. (Box 2, Folder 8)